{
    "id": "588532925fbc45d6939eb6f7b915068b",
    "title": "Conditional Forms Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "If I knew he was in trouble, I ……………….. him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will help",
                "would help",
                "would have helped"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b0d360ff06e04b22b2ab9567d895efd6"
        },
        {
            "question": "If she ………………. more politely, I would lend her my car.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "asks",
                "asked",
                "had asked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4c24ca5fb0ba4e1cab55636829c0361d"
        },
        {
            "question": "If he ………………….. me, I would have been in real trouble.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "doesn't help",
                "didn't help",
                "hadn't helped"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f8721443f8604e9495ac8a6f26d7dfdc"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I had known his name, I ………………… you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will tell",
                "would tell",
                "would have told"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d90141884cd84d2abedd28e127051e23"
        },
        {
            "question": "If she ………………… prompt medical attention, she would have survived.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "received",
                "has received",
                "had received"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b8d711c4360f4cd1a688acbbcf30ceaf"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I were you, I ……………… that examined by a doctor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will get",
                "would get",
                "would have got"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f82a36c7b8504c6eaf999937db343b5e"
        },
        {
            "question": "If the weather stays good, we ……………….. a game of tennis.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would play",
                "will play",
                "would have played"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "639a5dac53064d08ac74addfc6474aab"
        },
        {
            "question": "If she …………………. on time, she would have received the job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "applied",
                "applies",
                "had applied"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a8ff00d7311842da93340ba50021639d"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I ……………… you what happened, will you keep it to yourself?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tell",
                "told",
                "had told"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a118b07cb0ca4dc88710bdecbc3933cc"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I were you, I ………………. celebrating this occasion.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will be",
                "would",
                "would be"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1a02461de123468891cac7fb3a8eee3e"
        }
    ]
}